ethiotender.com 2012-12-27

# E-Tender Copyright and Privacy Policy

1\. Introduction

This service, hosted at www.ethiotender.com (hereunder stated at “site”) is a web technology based service owned and operated by Beam IT Solutions PLC, a private limited company formed under the Ethiopian Law. This site is intended to provide tender information that might be of interest to users. The contents of this Site, including but not limited to the text and images herein and their arrangements, unless otherwise noted, are the copyrighted material of Beam IT Solutions PLC. All rights reserved. All Trademarks referred to and hosted on our site are the property of their respective owners.

2\. Privacy Policy

> **A. General Information**
> 
> The following privacy policy guidelines apply to E-Tender ([www.ethiotender.com](http://www.ethiotender.com/)) and Beam IT Solutions PLC respects your right to privacy and keeps all your personal or company information confidential, unless you agree that some information about you or your respective company can be disclosed.
> 
> **B. Registration**
> 
> Registration is not required to gain access to E-Tender (www.ethiotender.com). However, there are sections of the web site which are accessible only to members of Beam IT Solutions PLC that do require registration as a member. Please see the “Subscribe” section of the web site for further information on becoming a member.
> 
> **C. Your Account**
> 
> When establishing a membership account with E-Tender or requesting information from our website, you will be asked to submit online application with your personal and/or company information. Though some information are mandatory providing full information may be optional; however, the more we know about you, the better we can provide the services you want most and best serve your business needs. Some of the information you provide might help your business be reached by tender posting companies and/or other companies that might require your good, products and/or services. Thus, you may opt to disclose some information about you and/or your company.
> 
> Beam IT Solutions PLC uses your contact information to respond to your e-mail requests and to reach you if we need additional information to complete your service request.
> 
> **D. Personal Information**
> 
> We may collect personal information from you including phone, electronic mail address, and other information you choose to provide. Beam IT Solutions PLC uses the personal information it collects online to process your requests, inform you of opportunities that we believe you might find interesting, and to understand your needs so that we can provide you with the highest quality of service. Beam IT Solutions PLC intends to protect and secure the personal information that you submit to this Site. Our Company will not sell, distribute, or give your personal information to any third party without your knowledge and consent.
> 
> **E. Policies on Other Sites**
> 
> Beam IT Solutions PLC has no control over, nor does it bear any of the responsibility for the privacy policies and/or content of any sites or advertisers linked to or presented on our website. Beam IT Solutions PLC also takes no responsibility for the “cookies” these sites or advertisers might deposit on your hard drive.

3\. Copyright 

The contents of this site, including but not limited to the text and images herein and their arrangements, unless otherwise noted, are the copyrighted material of Beam IT Solutions PLC. All rights reserved. All Trademarks referred to and hosted on our site are the property of their respective owners. If you propose to use any material (example Logo, Pictures, Advertisements, etc) on this site for any other purpose, you should request a written permission from Beam IT Solutions PLC in writing to the address indicated down below.

4\. Contact Information

If you have questions or concerns regarding E-Tender: please contact us by sending an e-mail to: [contact@ethiotender.com](mailto:contact@ethiotender.com) / [marketing@ethiotender.com](mailto:marketing@ethiotender.com)

You may also contact us:

  * **By Telephone:**

            +251 11 466 2694 / +251 91 134 3426 / +251 91 143 9458

  * **By Fax:**

            +251 11 467 1375

  * **By Regular Mail:**

> Beam IT Solutions PLC  
>  P. O. Box 2866 Code 1250  
>  Addis Ababa  
>  Ethiopia
